Guide to the Stuart Sherman Papers, 1945-2001 (Bulk 1961-2001) MSS.192
Fales Library and Special Collections
Stuart Sherman Papers
1945-2001
1961-2001
Fales Library and Special Collections
Sherman, Stuart, 1945-2001
Bradford, Mark
MSS.192
50.8 Linear Feet in 21 record cartons, 2 half manuscript boxes, 3 box binders, 1 LP box, 1 flat box, 63 jewel cases, and 1 shared card box.
28.8 Megabytes in 23 floppy disks.
63 DVDs
The Stuart Sherman Papers include material pertaining to his career as a performance and visual artist, poet, actor, and filmmaker. The collection is largely composed of material related to Sherman's artistic output including performance plans, prose and poetry, sketches and diagrams for visual and performance works, drafts for sculpture, photographs, slides, video, film, audio, and floppy disks. Personal material such as correspondence, journal writing, legal and financial documents along with works by fellow artists and writers also make up a large portion of the collection. The material spans from 1945-2001 with the bulk of it covering from 1961-2001.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Mark Bradford, executor of Stuart Sherman's Estate, in 2007. The accession number associated with this gift is 2007.192.
Arrangement
For the most part materials are arranged as they were received.
All efforts were made to preserve the original arrangement of the collection.
Series
Series I: Personal
Series II: Legal and Financial
Series III: Prose, Poetry and Other Writing
Series IV: Performance
Series V: Works by Others
Series VI: Artwork
Series VII: Photographs
Series VIII: Slides
Series IX: Video
Series X: Film
Series XI: Audio
Series XII: Misc. Media
Series XIII: Objects
Oversize Series
Biographical Note
Stuart A. Sherman was a performance artist, playwright, filmmaker, videographer, poet, essayist, sculptor and collagist. He was born 9 November 1945 to Helen Gordon and Samuel Sherman in Providence, Rhode Island. Soon after attending Antioch College in Yellow Springs, Ohio, Sherman moved to Manhattan and began a career in the arts which would span the next three decades. Before mounting his own work, Stuart Sherman worked extensively with Charles Ludlam in the early days of the Ridiculous Theatrical Company and with Richard Foreman's Ontological-Hysteric Theatre (Sherman appeared as Max in Foreman's "Pain(t)" in 1974).
Sherman was possibly best known for his solo "spectacles": programs of very short playlets performed on tabletops, in which he would physically manipulate and create semantic "dramas" around inanimate objects. He created and performed eighteen "spectacles" in all (12 solo and 6 group performances) as well as larger-scale dramatic works, including "Chekhov, Brecht and Strindberg" (1985-86), a trilogy of short plays adapting and commenting obliquely on those authors, "Slant (concerning Emily Dickinson)" (1987), and "Solaris" (1992).
Stuart Sherman also made over forty films and videos (rarely lasting more than five minutes), many of the most haunting of which were portraits of friends: Portrait of Benedicte Pesle (1984), Mr. Ashley Proposes (Portrait of George) (1985), Liberation (Portrait of Berenice Reynaud) (1993), and the 73-second Edwin Denby (1978). Nearly all of Stuart Sherman's film works are in the permanent collection of the Museum of Modern Art. Although best known for his performances and video, Sherman practiced in a variety of visual and literary mediums. He considered all of his artistic practices to share a performative dimension, and denied any guiding aesthetic principle. Sherman was wary of attributing any strict meaning to his work and assumed an essential polysemy in its interpretation. This assumption critically aligned Sherman's work with that of many of his downtown contemporaries.
Akin to the many distinct forms his art took, Sherman's work found an international audience. Although perhaps most at home with his New York contemporaries, he performed, exhibited, and lectured throughout the US (San Francisco, Cambridge, Boston, Indianapolis, Chicago) and abroad (Germany, Holland, The Netherlands, France, Wales, Japan, Australia).
Stuart Sherman received numerous awards for his work, including a Prix de Rome, a Guggenheim Fellowship, an Obie, a MacDowell Colony fellowship, an Asian Cultural Council Grant, a DAAD Grant for residency in Berlin and grants from the National Endowment for the Arts.
Sherman died of AIDS in San Francisco on 14 September 2001.
Stage Works:
- First Spectacle (1975)
- Second Spectacle (with Stefan Brecht, Richard Foreman, Kate Manheim) (1976)
- Seventh Spectacle (with 30 performers) (1976)
- Tenth Spectacle (Portraits of Places) (1978)
- Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic) (1979)
- Twelfth Spectacle (Language) (1980)
- Thirteenth Spectacle (Time) (1980)
- First Trilogy: Hamlet, Oedipus, Faust (1981-84)
- Second Trilogy: Chekhov, Strindberg, Brecht (1985-86)
- The Man in Room 2538 (1986)
- It Is Against the Law To Shout "Fire" In A Crowded Theater (1986)
- Endless Meadow and So Forth (1986)
- This House Is Mine Because I Live In It (1986)
- Slant (concerning Emily Dickinson) (1987)
- Crime and Punishment, or the Book and the Word (1987)
- "A" Is For Actor (1987)
- The Yellow Chair (1987)
- But What Is The Word For "Bicycle"? (1988)
- The Play of Tea, or Pinkies Up! (1989)
- Objects of Desire (1989)
- Knock, Knock, Knock, Knock (1989)
- Fourteenth Spectacle (1989)
- Taal Eulenspiegel (1990)
- Fifteenth Spectacle (1991)
- Sixteenth Spectacle (It's a Musical!) (La Mama E.T.C., March 18, 1991)
- Solaris (1992)
- Seventeenth Spectacle (Yes and Noh) (1993)
- Eighteenth Spectacle (The Spaghetti Works) (1993)
- Nineteenth Spectacle (But Second Musical) (La MaMa E.T.C., Jan. 10, 1994)
- Queer Spectacle (1994)
- The Stations of the Cross, or the passion of Stuart (2000)
Filmography:
- Globes (1977), 2:41
- Scotty and Stuart (1977), 2:22
- Skating (1978), 2:44
- Tree Film (1978), 1:30
- Edwin Denby (1978), 1:13
- Camera/Cage (1978), 2:57
- Flying (1979), 0:50
- Baseball/TV (1979), 1:12
- Hand/Water (1979), 1:37
- Piano/Music (1979), 1:17
- Roller Coaster/Reading (1979), 3:00
- Fountain/Car (1980), 0:39
- Rock/String (1980), 0:55
- Elevator/Dance (1980), 3:12
- Theatre Piece (1980), 0:52
- Bridge Film (1981), 1:20
- Racing (1981), 1:05
- Typewriting (Pertaining to Stefan Brecht) (1982), 2:06
- Chess (1982), 1:20
- Golf Film (1982)
- Fish Story (1983), 0:52
- Portrait of Benedicte Pesle (1984), 0:56
- Mr. Ashley Proposes (Portrait of George) (1985), 1:35
- Eating (1986), 6:10
- The Discovery of the Phonograph (1986), 6 min
- Scotty Snyder (All Around the Table) (1987), 10:13
- Berlin Tour (1988), 12 min
- Black-Eyed Susan (Portrait of an Actress) (1989), 9 min
- Liberation (Portrait of Berenice Reynaud) (1993), 8 min
Videography:
- Five Flowers (1982)
- Berlin (West)/Andere Richtungen (1986)
- Gray Matter (1987)
- Video Walk (1987)
- Yes and Noh Karaoke (1993)
- Scaffolding (1993)
- Don't Hang Up, I'm Freezing (1994)
- A Glass of Fish (1994)
- Cheers! (1994)
- Two Pixel Videos (Black and White/Grain) (1994)
- The Leap (1994)
- Bill Rice's Beer Garden (1994)
- Son of Scotty and Stuart (1994)
- Me and Joe (1994)
- 8 Eggs (1994)
- Pull (A Portrait of David Nunemaker) (1994)
- News Break (1994)
- Holy Bible (1994)
- Ah-Choo (1994)
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Access DVDs for audiovisual materials in the collection are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only.
Some audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact fales.library@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Born-digital materials have not been transferred and may not be available to researchers. Researchers may request access copies. To request that material be transferred, or if you are unsure if material has been transferred, please contact fales.library@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
Creative Time Archive (MSS.179)
Jaime Davidovich Collection (MSS.155)
Richard Foreman Papers (MSS.152)
Scope and Contents
The Stuart Sherman Papers include material pertaining to his career as a performance and visual artist, writer, actor, and filmmaker. The collection is largely composed of material related to Sherman's artistic output including performance plans, prose and poetry, sketches and diagrams for visual and performance works, drafts for sculpture, photographs, slides, video, film, audio, and floppy disks. Personal material such as correspondence, journal writing, legal and financial documents along with works by fellow artists and writers also make up a large portion of the collection. The material spans from 1945-2001 with the bulk of it covering from 1961-2001. The original order and description of material has largely been preserved and in most cases has been arranged chronologically. Thirteen series and one oversize series divide the collection into subgroups for the convenience of the researcher.
The Stuart Sherman Papers are divided into thirteen series:
SERIES I: Personal consists of personal items and documents including correspondence, resumes, and various material for psychological/spiritual healing.
SERIES II: Legal and Financial includes legal and financial documentation such as apartment leases, tax returns, bank account information, and Sherman's will.
SERIES III: Prose, Poetry and Other Writing contains much of Sherman's creative writing from his teenage years up until his death. The material has been ordered chronologically in groups respective of the arrangement as received: Juvenilia; Notes and Poetry; Reviews and Prose; Poetry; and Diagram Poetry. Although attempts were made to isolate these groups within this series, researchers may find Sherman's poetry and prose mixed throughout the collection. For example, poetry may be found in address books, in notebooks titled prose writing, alongside performance planning, or in other places.
SERIES IV: Performance consists of material related to Sherman's performances including written plans, diagrams, programs, correspondence, promotional material, and press.
SERIES V: Works by Others includes works by artists and writers other than Stuart Sherman which were included in his personal archive. Artworks, books, academic/professional journals, exhibition catalogs, and other miscellaneous items may be found in this series.
SERIES VI: Artworks consists of works of art by Stuart Sherman including drawings, sketches and drafts for sculpture, collage, as well as notes for visual art works. Two folders of mold damaged artworks have been removed from the bulk of other artworks and given a separate box.
SERIES VII: Photographic Materials includes all negatives, transparencies, contact sheets, and photographic prints from the collection. Some prints and contact sheets include photographer name, performance title, date and other identifying information.
SERIES VIII: Slides includes two binders of slides documenting Sherman's artistic output. The original order of slides has been preserved, though no obvious rule of arrangement appears to have existed. Some slides include detailed identifying information.
SERIES IX: Video contains all videotaped material by or pertaining to Stuart Sherman. Paper material which was found within original video containers may be found in Subseries C. Of the media portion, researcher access is limited to Subseries A: Video Recordings – Access Copies. Please contact a Fales archivist.
Subseries A: Video - Access Copies
Subseries B: Video - Originals
Subseries C: Video - Paper Material
SERIES X: Film contains all film from the collection. Researcher access is limited to Subseries A: Film - Access Copies. Please contact a Fales archivist.
Subseries A: Film - Access Copies
Subseries B: Film - Originals
SERIES XI: Audio includes all audio material in the collection. Audio recordings by Sherman may be found in Subseries A and B. Researcher access is limited to Subseries A: Audio - Access Copies. Commercial recordings owned by Sherman are included in Subseries C. Please contact a Fales archivist.
Subseries A: Audio - Access Copies
Subseries B: Audio - Originals
Subseries C: Audio - Works by Others
SERIES XII: Miscellaneous Media includes floppy disks.
SERIES XIII: Objects contains the few objects held within the collection.
OVERSIZE SERIES includes one large poster and several large artworks.
Series IV: Performance
Series VI: Artwork
Performance artists.; Art, American -- New York (State) -- 20th century.; Art -- Exhibitions -- New York (N.Y.); Experimental theater -- New York (N.Y.); Public art -- New York (N.Y.); Performance art -- New York (State) -- New York -- Exhibitions.; Artists -- New York (N.Y.); Bradford, Mark; Zummer, Thomas; Brecht, Stefan, 1924-2009; Foreman, Richard; Manheim, Kate
- Series I: Personal
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of personal items and documents including correspondence, resumes, and various material for psychological/spiritual healing.
  - Misc. Personal items - birth certificate, passport, driver's license, credit card, social security card, library cards, travel etc. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Address and Telephone Book, N/A (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Addresses - e-mail, phone numbers, business cards etc., N/A (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Resumes, N/A (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Astroflash Computer Horoscope, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fulbright Scholar Program Application [blank], 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Coping - misc. spiritual and psychologial healing materials, N/A (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - misc., 1971-1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - misc., 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - to Stuart Sherman and Mark Bradford, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - George Lesching to Mark Bradford; incl. press, German trans. Of "What is the Word for Bicycle" performance and "Solaris" by Sherman and Lesching, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - misc., N/A (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Series II: Legal and Financial
  This series consists of legal and financial documentation such as apartment leases, tax returns, bank account information, and Sherman's will.
  - Financial - Receipts, Bank info., etc. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Financial - Bank account registers - 1/28/98-12/16/98; 4/30/97-8/17/99; 8/18/99-5/9/00, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Legal - Will, Bankruptcy files, NYPL donation acknowledgements etc. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Apartment Leases, 1974-2001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Tax Returns, 1993-2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Series III: Prose, Poetry, and Other Writing
  This series includes prose, poetry, reviews, and other creative writing by Stuart Sherman from his teenage years up until his death.
  Arrangement
  The material has been ordered chronologically in groups respective of the arrangement as received: Juvenilia; Notes and Poetry; Reviews and Prose; Poetry; and Diagram Poetry. Although attempts were made to isolate these groups within this series, researchers may find Sherman's poetry and prose mixed throughout the collection. For example, poetry may be found in address books, in notebooks titled prose writing, alongside performance planning, or in other places.
  - Juvenilia - Riverdale Country School - literary journals, review papers, and undated school assignment, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Juvenilia - Misc. Writings and Poetry, 1962-1968 - loose sheets (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Juvenilia - Misc. Writings and Poetry, 1969-1972 - loose sheets (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Juvenilia - Misc. Writings and Poetry, 1970-1971 - notebooks [2] (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Juvenilia - Misc. Writings and Poetry, 1971-197? - notebook w/ inserted loose sheets (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Juvenilia - Misc. Writings and Poetry, undated - loose sheets (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Juvenilia - Misc. Writings and Poetry, undated - loose sheets (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Juvenilia - Misc. Writings and Poetry, undated - loose sheets (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Journals - loose sheets, 1977, 1985, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Misc. Notes and Poetry - notebooks [4], [circa 2000] (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Misc. Notes and Poetry - loose sheets and notebook, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Misc. Notes and Poetry - loose sheets and notebooks [3] [orig. folder: "What-have-you (What-had-he)"], undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Misc. Notes and Poetry - loose sheets, includes phone numbers, e-mail addresses, etc., undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Reviews by Stuart Sherman - incl. drafts and published versions, N/A (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Quotidian Review, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Prose Writing - 1985-1993 - loose sheets and notebook (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Prose Writing - 1994-2000 - loose sheets and notebook (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Prose Writing - undated - loose sheets (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - "Away From Here, or, There" - drafts, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Draft and Notes for unidentified writing, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Poetry - 1985-1991 - loose sheets (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Poetry - 1992-1993 - loose sheets (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Poetry - 1994-1998 - loose sheets (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Poetry - Inflatable Magazine #4 (Summer 1997) (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Poetry - 8/21/98-1/6/00 - loose sheets, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Poetry - Jan - July 2000 - loose sheets (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Poetry - 1/7/00-1/15/00; 6/12/00-8/10/00 - notebook, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Poetry - 4/28/00-5/31/00; 8/12/00-11/21/00 - notebook, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Poetry - Aug - Dec 2000 - loose sheets (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Poetry - 11/21/00-12/30/00 - notebook, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Poetry - 12/30/00-4/18/01- notebook, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Poetry - Jan - Mar 2001 - loose sheets (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Poetry - 4/18/01-8/9/01 - notebook, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Poetry - undated - loose sheets and notebook (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Diagram Poetry - untitled [53 paginated sheets w/ envelope postmarked 1971] (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Diagram Poetry - "WORD" [23 paginated sheets], undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Diagram Poetry - untitled [307 paginated sheets], undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Diagram Poetry - untitled A-Z [4 unique copies], undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Diagram Poetry - Misc., undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Diagram Poetry - Misc., undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Diagram Poetry - Misc., undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Series IV: Performance
  This series consists of paper materials relating to Stuart Sherman performances including written plans, diagrams, programs, correspondence, promotional material, and press.
  - Performance - "Cough", Discordia [notes, diagrams, correspondence, proposal, photograph], 1995 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Performance - "The Stations of the Cross, or, the Passion of Stuart" [notes, diagrams, contract, notebook etc.], circa 2000 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Performance - Proposal for Whitney Museum installation, drawn by R.D. Lloyd, undated (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Misc. Performance - notes and diagrams, circa 2000 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Misc. Performance - notes, diagrams, photographs and correspondence, N/A (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Misc. Performance - notes and writing, N/A (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Performance, film, video, and sound scripts w/ notes, N/A (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Programs and Promotional Material, 1983-2000 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Programs and Promotional Material, 1983-2000 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Program - "Artistic Boundaries Crossed: Symposium on Object Theatre," Amsterdam - incl. articles by and about Sherman, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Program - "Memorial Spectacle," Millenium Film Workshop, 7 June 2002 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Promo sheet - "The Eleventh Spectacle" [glasses], undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Promo sheet - "The Twelfth Spectacle" [glasses], undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Promo sheet - "The Thirteenth Spectacle" [glasses], undated (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Misc. Press, 1983-1997 (Box 4, Folder 73)
- Series V: Works by Others
  This series consists of works by artists and writers other than Stuart Sherman which were included in his personal archive. Artworks, books, academic/professional journals, exhibition catalogs, and other miscellaneous items may be found in this series. Some publications include contributions by or about Stuart Sherman.
  - Drawings "for Stuart" [by Tom Zummer?], 1986, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Drawings by Tom Zummer signed to Stuart, from "Discourse" 11.2 (Spring-Summer 1989) (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Scotty Snyder list of works, 1969-1995 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Written works by Bob Fleischner [2], undated (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Written works by John Matturri [2], undated (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Art book - Claudio Goulart, [untitled] Amsterdam, August 1982 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Art book - Tim Etchells, "Repeat Forever", undated (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Art book - Kate Manheim, "The Joy of Cooking" (An Infinity Etc Book), undated (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Mailing - Tripod Depot mailing [misc. typed works], 1992 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Mailing - Tripod Depot [e-mail and misc. typed works], 1998 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Mailing - Tripod Depot mailing - "The Holy Bible", 2001 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Misc. writings, resumes, script, artwork, recommendation, etc., N/A (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Publication - Julian Maynard Smith, Ken Wilder, "Spaces and Narrations" (97-99 Gallery) exhibit catalog, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Publication - Stefan Brecht, Poems, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Publication - Performance Art magazine 2, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Publication - See/Saw magazine 1 (Winter '81-'82), 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Publication - Object Theatre: Body and Object, Blue Report 6 (Amsterdam: Theater Instituut Nederland, December 1998) (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Publication - Millenium Film Journal, No. 34 (Fall 1999); No.35/36 (Fall 2000), 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Publication - Canyon Cinema, Film/Video Catalog, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Publication - Quentin Bertoux and Jean-Marc Adolphe, ALIS (Maison de la Culture d'Amiens et ALIS, 2000) (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Publication - Noel Sheridan, "On Reflection" (Four Courts Press), includes selection by Stuart: "Performance, Perth, 1991" [book was discarded due to excessive mold and irreparable water damage; notes from author to Stuart have been photocopied], undated (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Publication - Hamlet, annotated copy w/ loose notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Publication - The Chapel Hymnal (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Trading Cards - "Ideas in Motion" John Davis, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 97)
- Series VI: Artwork
  This series includes drawings, sketches, drafts for sculpture, collage, and other artworks. Sixty-nine original drafts (Folders 120 and 121) were treated for mold damage and have been housed separately (Box 5B). Several works had post-it annotations attached, which have been photocopied and removed. The photocopies are housed next to the corresponding draft.
  - Notes for artworks - to-do lists, undated (Box 5A, Folder 98)
  - Drawings w/ exhibition card - Paula Allen Gallery, 11/30/89-12/23/89, 1987, 1989 (Box 5A, Folder 99)
  - Drawings, Sketches for Sculpture, Notes, 1986-1995 (Box 5A, Folder 100)
  - Drawings, Sketches for Sculpture, Notes, 1987 (Box 5A, Folder 101)
  - Drawings, Sketches for Sculpture, Notes, 1988 (Box 5A, Folder 102)
  - Drawings, Sketches for Sculpture, Notes, 1988-1989 (Box 5A, Folder 103)